《生化危机：来生》
我叫艾莉丝
My name is Alice.
我曾任职雨伞企业秘密实验室
I worked for Umbrella Corporation in a secret laboratory...
发展实验性生化武器
...developing experimental viral weaponry.
不过发生了意外，病毒扩散
There was an incident. A virus escaped.
大家都死了
Everybody died.
问题是
Trouble was...
他们并没有死透
...they didn't stay dead.
这是病毒爆发，地球浩劫的开始
This was the start of an apocalypse that would sweep the entire world.
该为此灾难负责的人却躲入地下
The men responsible for this disaster took refuge underground...
继续实验致命的T病毒
...and continued to experiment with the deadly T-Virus.
他们以为在高科技碉堡里很安全
They felt secure in their high-tech fortress.
可是他们错了
But they were wrong.
（四年后）
僵尸歼灭
Biohazard terminated.
涉谷中区
Central Shibuya.
确认？
Confirm?
确认
I confirm.
枪法真准
Nice shooting.
目前我三比一赢
And l lead three to one.
时间还早
The night is young.
还有很多机会
Plenty more fish in the...
俊，你没事吧？
Toshi, are you okay?
俊，你在哪里？
Toshi, where are you?
（东京 雨伞企业总部）
3号请回答
Sentry three respond.
又一个人失联了
We lost contact with another one.
- 魏斯克主席 - 报告
- Chairman Wesker. - Report.
长官，半小时前
Sir, a half-hour ago, we began to lose contact...
总部周边部份哨兵失联
...with some of our perimeter sentries.
有多少人失联？
How many have we lost?
全部
All of them.
你等了半小时才向我报告？
And you waited 30 minutes to tell me?
我们以为是通讯问题
We thought it was communications problem.
我不想打扰您
l didn't want to disturb you.
联络地面大门
Give me the surface gate.
- 我是魏斯克主席 - 长官
- This is Chairman Wesker. - Sir.
报告你的状况
Report your situation.
这里很平静
Everything is quiet here.
没有入侵迹象？
No sign of intruders?
- 穗高！ - 有动静
- Hotaka. - We have movement.
多重目标
Multiple targets.
地面大门，确认目标
Surface gate, identify targets.
重覆，确认目标
Repeat, identify targets.
长官，二号电梯有动静
Sir, Elevator 2 is moving.
警卫立刻前往主要入口
l want security at that entrance.
嘿！老弟
Hey, boys.
你们男生都这样欺负女生吗？
ls that any way to treat a lady?
叫警卫用神经毒气灌满主要入口
Tell security to flood the main entrance with nerve gas.
长官，我们的人还在上面
Sir, our men are still up there.
还有别的问题吗？
Any more questions?
第一至第五区、第七区、第八区 都有入侵者
lntruders in Sectors 1 through 5, 7 and 8.
据报第十区和第十一区传出枪声
Reports of gunfire in Sectors 10 and 11 .
各单位坚守岗位
Stay at your stations.
所有安全措施全面启动
All security protocols are now in full effect.
封闭所有电梯
Lock down all elevators.
封锁内部防爆门
Seal all internal blast doors.
我还要损害报告
And l want damage reports.
（净化设施 倒数开始）
快点，快跑
Come on, move.
- 快！快！ - 大家快跑
- Go, go. Everybody... - Get out.
乱流、乱流、乱流
Turbulence. Turbulence. Turbulence.
乱流
Turbulence. Turbulence.
Turbulence. Turb...
你有什么遗言？
Any last words?
真高兴能见到真正的你
How nice to finally meet the real you.
很痛，对吧？
Hurts, doesn't it?
这只是你走霉运的开始
Well, that's just the start of the bad news.
你拥有的所有能力
All those powers of yours:
速度、力量、快速自愈能力
Speed, strength, accelerated healing.
这些你全都没了
Well, you can kiss all those goodbye.
- 你动了什么手脚？ - 我帮你注射的血清
- What have you done? - The serum l've injected you with is
正在中和你体内的T细胞
neutralizing the T cells in your body.
这只是
Put simply...
雨伞企业收回它的资产
...the Umbrella Corporation is taking back its property.
你的表现不如预期
You just didn't work out,
所以就被召回了
so you're being recalled
现在我拥有你的能力
l'm what you used to be.
只不过比你更强
Only better.
请等一下
Please wait.
有遗言吗？
Last words?
谢谢你
Thank you.
谢我杀你？
For killing you?
谢谢你让我再度成为人类
For making me human again.
地面迫近，拉高
Pull up. Terrain. Terrain. Pull up. Terrain. Terrain.
这是亚凯地以紧急频道广播
This is Arcadia, broadcasting on the emergency frequency.
这里没有感染
There is no infection.
我们提供安全、食物和庇护
We offer safety and security, food and shelter.
（六个月后）
这是亚凯地以紧急频道广播
This is Arcadia, broadcasting on the emergency frequency.
这里没有感染
There is no infection.
在我向保护伞展开复仇时
While I took revenge on Umbrella...
最后一批幸存者搭直升机去避难
...the last handful of survivors took a chopper to safety.
他们前往阿拉斯加的亚凯地
They were headed for a town in Alaska called Arcadia.
我们接收到那里发出的广播
We'd received radio transmissions from there.
他们提供安全、食物和庇护
They offered food and shelter, safety and security.
一个没有感染的避难所
A haven, free of infection.
五月三日16点
May 3rd, 1600 hours.
177天没有任何生命迹象
A hundred and seventy-seven days without signs of life.
我在北纬58点37度
l'm at 58.37 degrees north,
西经134点58度
134.58 degrees west.
接近亚凯地的座标
Closing in on the coordinates for Arcadia,
不过却完全找不到它
but no signs of it on any map.
希望克莱儿和其他人成功抵达
l hope Claire and the others made it.
你不来吗？
You're not coming?
照顾大家
Take care of the others.
祝你好运，家乐福
Good luck, K-Mart.
克莱儿
Claire.
五月三日19点30分
May 3rd. 1930 hours.
亚凯地
Arcadia.
这个地方根本不存在
No such place exists.
只有一片空地
Just an empty field.
和一片海滩
And a beach.
可是我们都听见广播了
But we all heard the transmissions.
一定有人传送出广播
Someone must have sent them.
一定有人吸引所有人来此
Someone must have brought all these people here.
可是为什么？
But why?
他们又跑去哪里了？
And where did they go?
第177天，纪录完毕
Day 177. Signing off.
我不知道我能不能撑下去
l don't know if l can do this much longer.
如果我是最后一个，只剩我一个
What if l'm the last one? What if there is no one else?
不会再有人看这些影像呢？
No one to watch these tapes.
难道这是惩罚
ls this my punishment...
惩罚我造成这一切？
...for letting all this happen?
嘿，等等
Hey. Wait!
等等！拜托，停下来！
Wait, please! Stop!
哈啰？
Hello.
Hello?
回答我
Answer me.
嘿，嘿
Hey, hey.
没关系
lt's okay.
对不起
Sorry about that.
不过我得把这玩意从你身上拿掉
But l had to get this thing off of you.
这是什么？是谁下的手？
What is this? Who did this to you?
你知道我是谁吗？
Do you even know who l am?
我叫艾莉丝
My name is Alice.
我们18个月前在内华达沙漠认识
We met in the Nevada desert 18 months ago.
你有印象吗？
Any of this sound familiar?
麦基、卡洛斯、LJ？
Mikey, Carlos, L.J.?
家乐福？
K-Mart?
你和一群幸存者搭上直升机
You left in a helicopter...
飞往阿拉斯加
...with a group of survivors headed for Alaska.
亚凯地，记得吗？
Arcadia, remember?
五月四日8点
May 4th, 0800 hours.
标出航道前往英属哥伦比亚 鲁珀特王子港
Plotting a course for Prince Rupert in British Columbia.
我要经由温哥华前往西雅图
l'll pass Vancouver, drop down to Seattle.
之后就是旧金山
After that, it's San Francisco
以及其他西岸城市
and the rest of the Western seaboard.
我的乘客依然健谈如昔
My passenger is still as talkative as ever.
不论那玩意是什么
Whatever that thing was...
它都在注射某种药物
...it was injecting her with some sort of drug.
会造成记忆丧失
Something that causes memory loss.
我只希望药效不会是永久的
l just hope the effects aren't permanent.
你叫
Your name...
艾莉丝，对吧？
...is Alice, right?
她会说话了
She speaks.
刚刚的事很抱歉
Look, l'm sorry about back there.
我不知道出了什么事
l don't know what happened.
我什么都不记得了
l don't remember anything.
我甚至不知道我叫什么
l don't even know my name.
你叫克莱儿
lt's Claire.
克莱儿瑞菲尔德
Claire Redfield.
克莱儿？
Claire?
想起来了？
Sound familiar?
没有
Not really.
你会习惯的
You'll get used to it.
也许你可以帮我松绑了？
Perhaps you can cut me loose now.
我想我们最好先熟悉彼此再说
We should get to know each other a little better first.
天使之城
City of Angels.
五月六日18点，洛杉矶
May 6th, 1800 hours, Los Angeles.
没有生命迹象
No signs of life.
连僵尸都没有
Not even the undead.
有些人跟这个城市一起烧掉了
Some must have burnt with the city.
可是其他人呢？
But what about the rest?
我的老天
Oh, my God.
怎样？
What?
你看那边
Look over there.
要命
Damn.
有飞机，有飞机！
lt's a plane. lt's a plane!
我就知道
l knew it.
（救命）
我就说有人会来
I told you they would come.
我们在这里！哈啰！
Hey, we're down here. Hello!
我们根本不可能进去
No way we're getting in there.
他要去哪？怎么飞走了？
Where is he going? Why is he flying away?
他没有飞走，他在盘旋
It's not flying away. lt's circling.
盘旋
Circling?
靠，他飞好低
Damn, he's low.
趴下！
Down!
他在搞什么鬼？
What the hell is he doing?
他要降落，他要降落了
He's gonna land.
快清出跑道，快！快去！
He's gonna land. Get the stuff out of the way.
- 降落？ - 是啊，终于
- Land? - Yeah. Land.
这家伙一定是个疯子
That is one crazy son of a bitch.
这可能会有点颠簸
This may get a little rough.
那就替我松绑
Then cut me loose.
谢了
Thanks.
别乱来就好，好吗？
Just don't do anything crazy, all right?
看看你自己准备要做什么吧
Nothing as crazy as what you have in mind.
快点，金
Come on, Kim. Move it.
使劲推
Move it!
坐稳了
All right, hold on.
快点，他来了
Hurry, he's coming.
快点
Come on.
- 快拉！ - 快点，拉啊！
- Come on, pull it. Come on. - Come on, pull!
很好
Good. Good.
Good work.
很好，干的好
That's it. Good job.
降落的不错
Nice landing.
我想技术上来说，这是坠机
I think technically it's called crashing.
路瑟威斯
Luther West.
艾莉丝，那是克莱儿
Alice. That's Claire.
路德威斯，很高兴认识你
Luther West. A pleasure to make your acquaintance.
你好，我是克莉丝朵
Hi, my name's Crystal.
不用了，介绍够了
No, no. Enough with the introductions.
你是来救我们的吧？
So you're here to help us, right?
- 你能救我们出去吗？ - 你从亚凯地来的？
- Can you get us out? - You from Arcadia?
- 你说什么？ - 你从亚凯地来的吗？
- What did you say? - Are you from Arcadia?
你对亚凯地知道多少？
What do you know about Arcadia?
他们说他们能帮我们
They said they'd help.
那里还有其他幸存者 既文明又安全
There are survivors. Civilization and safety.
也没有感染
lnfection free.
所以是他们派你来的？
So they sent you, right?
- 不是 - 可是还有像你们一样的人吧？
- No. - But there are others out there like you?
只有我们了
lt's just us.
没有人会来救援？
There's to be no rescue?
对不起
l'm sorry.
- 对不起 - 别难过，他们只是怀抱期望
- Sorry. - Look, don't take it so bad. They had their hopes up and....
以为你可以带他们去人间净土
Thought you could take them to the promised land.
天使欧提兹
Angel Ortiz.
你飞得不错
That was some fine flying.
谢了
Thanks.
状况如何？
What's the prognosis?
它还撑得住
She'll live.
嗯
Yeah.
你知道 我有个很怪的感觉，我认识你
You know... I have the strangest feeling I know you.
我常听人这么说
Yeah, I get that a lot. You're a sports fan, huh?
你是运动迷吧？你喜欢篮球？
Do you like basketball?
不算是
Not really.
不是？
No?
也许是搜藏名表的爱表人士
Well, maybe just a fan of fine timepieces.
（巨星风采）
是啊，路瑟是我们的超级巨星
Yeah. Luther here is our resident superstar.
说说亚凯地的事吧
So tell me about Arcadia.
你们到底知道些什么？
What exactly do you know?
只是从广播里听到的
Just from their transmissions.
我们整个星期都在听他们的广播
We've been receiving their broadcast all week.
安全、食物和庇护，没有感染
Food and shelter, safety and security, no infection.
我们以为你是他们派来的
We thought they sent you.
我们一直发射信号弹吸引注意
We've been launching flares for days to get their attention.
- 信号弹？ - 是的
- Flares? - Yeah.
从阿拉斯加怎么看得到？
Who's gonna see flares from Alaska?
- 阿拉斯加？ - 阿拉斯加？
- Alaska? - Alaska?
我到过亚凯地，在阿拉斯加
Arcadia. l've been there.
- 那是个小镇，至少我们以为是 - 小镇？
- lt's in Alaska. lt's a town, or so we thought. - A town?
我不这么想
l don't think so.
你看
Take a look.
看哪里？
At what?
你看到了
You see?
那不是一个小镇
lt's not a town.
那是一艘船
lt's a ship.
我从短波收音机录下这个
l recorded this from the shortwave.
这是亚凯地以紧急频道广播
This is Arcadia, on the emergency frequency.
这里没有感染
There is no infection.
我们提供安全、食物和庇护
We offer safety and security, food and shelter.
跟我们听到的讯息一样
lt's the same message.
他们一定是沿海行驶，救助幸存者
They must have sailed the coast, picking up survivors.
这是亚凯地以紧急频道广播
This is Arcadia, broadcasting on the emergency frequency.
怎么回事？
What is that?
我不知道
l don't know.
那是我们最后听见的广播
That was the last we heard from them.
之后一切就停止了
Then it just stopped.
那是两天前的事了
That was two days ago.
我们每逢整点就打信号弹
We've been sending up flares on the hour.
所以我们以为你是他们派来的
So when you arrived, of course, we thought they sent you.
克莱儿
Claire.
那边那艘船
That ship over there.
那就是亚凯地
That's Arcadia.
我知道
l know.
你记起来了？
You remember?
我记得海滩
I remember the beach.
他们当时来救我们
People were coming to help us.
后来呢？你怎么没跟其他人去？
What happened? Why didn't you go with the others?
我不知道，我记不得了
l don't know. I can't remember.
我们得上那艘船才行
We have to get to that ship.
（堡垒监狱）
欢迎来到你的新家，B牢区
Welcome to your new home, cell block B.
克莉丝朵是我们的厨师
Crystal's our cook.
菜色不多，不过她手艺很好
The menu's not extensive, but she is a master of what she does.
抱歉没带来好消息
Sorry l didn't bring better news.
要习惯失望，我经纪人都这么说
Get used to disappointment, right? That's what my agent used to say.
你以前是演员？
Were you an actress?
我来好莱坞逐梦，却当了服务生
l came to Hollywood, ended up waiting tables.
还等什么？抱歉，我饿了，谢谢
Why are we waiting? Excuse me. l'm hungry. Thank you.
- 快滚啦 - 谢谢
- Get out of here, man. - Thank you.
我遇过很多像他一样的怪咖
l met plenty of creeps like him in my time.
他又有什么故事？
What's his story?
以前他算是王牌电影制片
Back in the world, he was some kind of big movie producer.
那家伙很难相处
The boy's got a stick up his ass.
金洋是他助理
Kim Yong used to intern for him.
他还没察觉世界已经变了
Still hasn't figured the world has changed.
你想你那架飞机还能飞吗？
That plane, do you think it could still fly?
还能飞，不过它只能载两个人
It can fly, but it only seats two.
那你可以一次载一个去亚凯地
So take us to Arcadia one at a time.
我想她能在这降落一次算走运
Look, l think she was lucky to land here once.
再来个五、六次就算自杀了
Five or six times would be suicide.
我没有恶意
No offense.
我不介意
None taken.
一定还有别的办法
There has to be another way out.
我们得上那艘船
We have to get to that ship.
是有啦
Well, there is the...
什么？
What?
没什么
Nothing.
这根本就是浪费你的时间
Look, it would be a waste of your time.
我有的是时间可以浪费
l have time to waste.
情况危急时，我们躲进监狱里
When the shit hit the fan, we took refuge in the prison.
监狱有最厚、最坚固的墙壁
It seemed like it had the biggest, strongest walls.
隔绝那些僵尸的最好防线
The best chance of keeping those things out.
我们到的时候
By the time we got here,
狱警和囚犯早就落跑了
the guards and inmates were already long gone.
我想
l guess
人们开始互相啃咬的时候
when people started eating one another...
囚禁谁也没意义了
...there wasn't much point in keeping anybody locked up.
我们以为这里都没人了
We thought the place was abandoned...
直到我们有了发现
...until we made a discovery.
温岱，该休息了
Wendell... ...time to take a break.
也该是时候了，我讨厌待在下面
lt's about goddamn time. l hate being down here.
我听到墙里面有动静
l'm hearing movement in the walls.
我们去看看
So let's check it out.
我马上回来
l'll be back in a minute.
来吧
Come on.
我叫克里斯
Name's Chris.
你是开飞机的那个人
You were the one flying that plane.
你怎么知道？
How do you know that?
不是只有温岱能听得见声音
Wendell isn't the only one that hears things.
很高兴你安全抵达
l'm glad you made it.
也许你能跟这些人讲道理
Maybe you can talk some sense into these people.
这话什么意思？
What do you mean?
不是很明显吗？
lsn't it obvious?
我不是囚犯
l'm not a prisoner.
我不该被关在这里
l shouldn't be in here.
我原本隶属于军事单位
l was working with a military unit.
我们以这里作为中继站
We were using this place as a staging post.
州长下令释放所有囚犯时
Things were already bad when the order came through...
状况已经很糟了
...to release all the inmates.
我们需要足够的人手
We needed as many people on the streets as possible...
打退那些僵尸
...to fight those things.
结果一团混乱
And it was chaos.
我们撤退，一群囚犯攻击我
We were pulling out and a gang of the prisoners jumped me.
我猜他们以为我是狱警
l guess they thought l was a guard.
等我醒来，我的部队早撤走了
l woke up, my unit was gone.
我就被关在这里
l was in here.
他们想开个玩笑
Their idea of a joke.
你不相信我
You don't believe me.
其他人信吗？
Do the others?
你得把我弄出去
You need to get me out of here.
无论如何，我们都被困在这里了
We're all trapped here.
是没错，不过我能帮你
That's true.But I can help you.
看够了？
Seen enough?
- 你有找到什么吗？ - 没有
- You find anything? - No.
我知道离开这里的方法
l know a way out of this place.
如果你帮我出去，我就帮你
lf you get me out of here, l'll do the same for you.
你会需要我的
You're gonna need me!
你查过他说的事吗？
Have you checked what he's talking about?
出去的方法？
His way out?
除非放了他，他什么都不会说
He's not telling us shit till we let him out.
我才不打算放他，这家伙是犯人
And l'm not letting him out.The man is a killer.
- 真的？ - 我从他眼神就看的出来
- Really? - l can see it in his eyes.
你怎能这么确定？
How can you be so sure?
我很清楚人性
l know people.
真有趣，告诉我
lnteresting. So tell me.
你从我的眼神之中看到什么？
What do you see when you look into my eyes?
我的妈呀！
Holy shit.
女人当自强
Girl's gotta be prepared.
你拿那些要干嘛？
What would you possibly want with those?
这是兴趣
lt's a hobby.
兴趣？
A hobby?
好吧
All right.
明天早上见
Well, l'll see you in the morning.
连个鬼影也没有
No sign of anyone on deck.
那里有你的朋友？
Your friends are out there?
我想是吧
l think so.
你记不起来了？
You don't remember?
我会记起来的
lt's coming back.
慢慢的
Slowly.
这没什么道理可言
Nothing that makes any sense.
我们还有自来水
We still have running water.
还真文明
That's very civilized.
我们尽力维持
We do our best.
好冷
lt's cold.
有水就不错了
Our best only goes so far.
- 这是给你的 - 谢谢
- These are for you. - Thank you.
我想我该让你自己来
l guess l should leave you to it.
我想也是
l guess you should.
我就在外面
l'll be right outside.
谢谢
Thank you.
路瑟
Luther?
- 冷静点，亲爱的 - 走
- Take it easy, honey. - Move it.
我正打算要走了
Okay, l'm just gonna be on my way now.
别激动
Okay, take it easy. Take it easy.
滚远一点
Get out of my sight.
这是什么味道？
What is that smell?
一定是从排水沟钻上来的
Must have burrowed up from the sewers.
温岱说他听到墙后面有声音
Wendell said he heard things moving.
所以这些僵尸 随时都能冒出来？
What? So these things can just burst out anywhere?
我们得离开这里
We gotta get out of this place.
亚凯地会派救兵来的
Arcadia will send help.
没人会来救我们的，没有人
No one's coming to get us. Okay? No one.
我们必须自救
We have to help ourselves.
你的那架飞机
This plane that you have.
- 它载不了所有人 - 我们可以抽签
- Won't hold everybody. - Well, we can draw straws.
不！我们都离开，不丢下任何人
No. We all get out of here and no one gets left behind.
太好了，我们要怎么做？
Great. How are we gonna do that?
直接排队走出去？
Walk out of here, just single file?
你疯了？
Are you crazy?
狱警也不愿意放他出来
They didn't want him getting out.
是啊，他很危险
He's dangerous.
安琪，你觉得呢？
Angel, what do you think?
我想我们没多少选择
l think we don't have much of a choice.
这太瞎了
This is insane.
克莉丝朵你觉得呢？
Crystal, Crystal, look at me. What do you think?
不会连你都那么蠢吧
I mean, not even you're that dumb.
我想我是很蠢
I guess l am.
我想的跟天使一样
l agree with Angel.
这家伙知道怎么出去，我想听听
lf this guy thinks he knows a way out, l wanna hear it.
好了
All right.
当真？
Seriously?
这是个错误
This is a mistake.
这是个天大的错误，你们最好盯紧他
This is a big mistake. You better keep your eyes on him.
我还在想到底会拖多久
l was wondering how long it would take.
- 我… - 好了，快点离开这里吧
- I... - All right, let's get the hell out of here.
- 克莱儿？ - 什么？
- Claire? - What?
是我
Claire, it's me.
我是克里斯
lt's Chris.
我不认识你
l don't know you.
克莱儿 我是你哥哥，记得吗？
Claire. l'm your brother, remember?
你是怎么了？
What the hell's happened to you?
没关系，让他走
lt's okay. Let him go.
她丧失记忆了
Look, she suffered some sort of memory loss.
如果你真是她哥，她会想起来的
lf you really are her brother... ...it'll come back.
这还真感人，手足团聚啊？
All right, this is touching. Family reunion.
趁我们还没被啃之前 能不能快点上路？
lf we could just get a move on, please, before we're all eaten the fuck alive.
门后有一辆镇暴车
Behind those doors is a UPV, urban pacification vehicle.
是监狱为了防范暴动发生准备的
The prison kept it in case of a serious riot.
十六轮、钢板、喷水枪
Sixteen-wheeler, steel plate, water cannon. It seats 20.
可乘坐20人，十顿重的玩具
Ten tons of fun.
我们威风地开出去压扁它们
We roll on out in style, drive right over them.
锁坏了，也许可以直接弄开门
The lock's jammed. But we can cut through it.
到了海边，我们就要换乘船只
When we hit the coast, we have to transfer to a boat.
我们需要更多武器
We're gonna need more firepower.
我有你需要的东西
I got you covered.
我们以前在地下室设了军火库
When l was stationed here, we used the basement as an armory.
那里有你想得到的各式武器
lt's got every weapon you can dream of.
你怎么知道 你部队撤退时没带走武器？
How do you know your unit didn't take them with them?
因为到最后
Because by the end...
武器的数量已经远多过活人了
...there were more guns than there were people to use them.
你去拿武器
You go get the guns. Luther.
我的天哪
Oh, my God.
这是什么？
What is this?
监狱用帮浦抽出地基里的水
They had pumps to keep the water out of the foundations.
后来电力中断
When the electricity failed,
部份较低楼层就开始进水
some of the lower levels started filling up.
下面还有两层
There's another two floors down there.
那军火库在哪里？
And how far down is the armory?
最下面那一层
All the way.
路瑟，快点！
Luther, come on.
退后！
Get back. Get back.
你想去哪里？
Where do you think you're going?
我高中时是游泳冠军
l was a swim champ back in high school.
是吗？
Is that right?
拿着
Here.
现在你信任我拿枪了？
You're gonna trust me with a gun?
是啊，有何不可？
Yeah. Why not?
快毙了那个怪物
Luther, just shoot that motherfucker.
那是什么鬼？
What the fuck is that thing?
（电梯）
好了，我们走
All right. Let's go.
我们走
Let's go.
赞啦！
Nice.
靠
Damn.
外面一定有好几百个僵尸
There must be hundreds of them out there.
不能往回走
We can't go back that way.
- 该死 - 你说该死是什么意思？
- Oh, shit. - What do you mean, "oh, shit"?
这是什么？
What? What is this?
你认为是什么？
What do you think it is?
别告诉我那玩意应该要装进去
Don't tell me that thing fits inside of there.
你能不能把这装回去？
Can you put this back together?
也许能，不过要一星期
Maybe, but it could take a week.
那现在怎么办？
What do we do now?
我知道
l know.
班奈特
Bennett...
你这是做什么？
...what have you done?
我们必须离开这里
Luther, we gotta get out of here. Come on.
你听见没？
Did you hear that?
- 快点，快啊 - 我们要干嘛？
- Come on, baby. Come on. - What are we doing?
我们要离开这里
Getting out.
- 不过其他人 - 叫他们去死！快上来！
- But the others. - Fuck the others. Now, get onboard.
你干嘛？
Bennett, what are you doing?
- 嘿! - 别这样！
- Hey! - Kim Yong! Don't do this.
开门！
Open this door.
班奈特，拜托
Bennett, please.
班奈特
Bennett!
该死！
Oh, shit!
这就对了！你去死吧！
That's right, bitch. Fuck you.
好耶！
Yes! Yes!
混帐东西
Son of a bitch.
对不起，对不起
l'm sorry. l'm so sorry.
他往亚凯地飞了
He's headed for the Arcadia.
艾莉丝
Alice.
走吧
Come on!
去淋浴区
Head for the shower block.
- 快点！ - 到那里会合
- Move. - I'll meet you there.
这玩意没动力
This thing has no power.
我们不需要动力
We won't need power.
糟糕！
Oh, shit.
抓稳了
Hold on!
快去淋浴区！快！
Hey, head to the shower block. Go.
这边！
Over here!
你没事吧？
Are you all right?
谢了
l'm fine. Thanks.
这是在开玩笑吧？
This is some kind of joke, right?
不，这些地道通往下水道
The tunnels lead to the sewers,
下水道又通往排水管
the sewers lead to the storm drain.
排水管则通往大海
This storm drain leads to the sea.
这是我们唯一的机会
lt's our only chance.
我先走
I'll take point.
我掩护你
l got your back.
女士们
Ladies.
好了，你跟上去
All right, you're next.
- 我做不到 - 你可以的
- I can't do it. - You can.
快走！
Let's go!
那些僵尸很靠近
Those things are close.
我们在前面找到一个出口
We found a way out just down there.
通道直接接上排水管
The tunnels drop into a storm drain.
去吧，小心点
Go. Be careful.
金洋呢？
Where's Kim Yong?
走吧
Go. Go.
我就知道你会成功
l knew you'd make it.
路瑟
Luther!
救我
Help!
路瑟
Luther!
你现在帮不了他了
You can't help him now.
我们必须前进
We have to move on.
没有欢迎大会啊？
No welcome party, huh?
看来班奈特飞到了
It looks like Bennett made it.
进去看看
Let's check inside.
- 你有找到人吗？ - 没有
- Did you find anyone? - Nothing.
我看了船员舱，他们都走了
l checked the crew quarters. They're all gone.
看来他们走得很匆忙
Looks like they left in a hurry.
这是亚凯地以紧急频道广播
This is Arcadia, broadcasting on the emergency frequency.
这里没有感染
There is no infection.
我们提供安全、食物和庇护
We offer safety and security, food and shelter.
油料、电力，全都正常运作
Fuel, power, everything's running normally.
你们看，是航海日志
Look at this. lt's the ship's log.
船员三天前坐上了救生艇
The crew launched the lifeboats three days ago.
就是广播中断的那天
Exactly when the transmissions stopped.
不过上面写着 船上还有两千名乘客
But it says there are still 2000 survivors onboard.
（救生艇）
我们要搜索船上的每个角落
We have to search every inch of this ship.
雨伞
Umbrella.
没错
Of course.
我记得他们来追我们
l remember them coming for us.
这整件事，亚凯地
This whole thing, Arcadia,
都是谎言
was a lie.
不，比那更糟
No, it's worse than that.
这是个陷阱
lt's a trap.
那些人都到哪儿去了呢？
Where is everybody?
我不明白
l don't understand.
我想我明白
l think l do.
他们就在我们脚下
They're underneath our feet.
他们囚禁幸存者，拿来做实验
They're holding survivors to experiment on them.
你看
Look.
是家乐福，她在这
lt's K-Mart. She's here.
把他们送上来
Bring them up.
全部都要
All of them.
她在这里
Here she is.
家乐福
K-Mart.
把她弄出来
Get her out.
家乐福，没事了
K-Mart, it's okay. lt's okay.
K-Mart, it's all right.
我来帮她弄掉这玩意
I'll get this off her.
你去放出其他人
Let everyone out.
我们是你朋友，现在我们需要你帮忙
We're your friends. Right now, we need your help.
让我帮你把这个拿掉吧
Let me get this off you.
（小心 请勿靠近）
我怎么一点也不意外？
Why am l not surprised?
你不是很难找
You weren't too hard to find.
我们的卫星系统仍然可以运作
Our satellite system is still operational.
现在也没什么人会飞了
And there aren't too many people flying nowadays.
何况
And besides,
我很清楚你一定会去找朋友
l always knew you'd be drawn to your friends.
还真有情义啊
Loyalty... ...highly overrated.
停
Stop.
坐下
Down.
我不想要你伤害我的宠物
Wouldn't want you harming my pets.
把枪放下
Drop your guns.
谢谢，踢过来给我
Thank you. Kick them to me.
很好
Good.
你气色不大好，班奈特
You don't look so good, Bennett.
是啊，我打算撕烂你美丽的脸
Yeah, l'm looking forward to playing with your pretty face.
你找我干嘛？
What do you want from me?
T病毒让我活过来
The T-Virus brought me back.
不过它太强了
But it's so strong.
它想控制我
It fights me for control.
我以为只要摄取新鲜的人类DNA
l thought if l ingested fresh human DNA...
就能恢复平衡
...l could redress the balance.
怪不得你的船员弃船落跑了
No wonder your crew abandoned ship.
无所谓
No matter.
我现在有了新的属下
Now l have a new subordinate.
还有一个新计划
And a new plan.
你是唯一和T病毒成功融合的人
You were the only one who successfully bonded with the T-Virus.
你的DNA比其他人的强壮
Your DNA is stronger than the others.
吃了你
l ingest you...
我就能取得控制权
...l gain control.
这招挺聪明的
That's pretty smart thinking.
不过只有一个问题
There's only one problem with that plan.
给我停在那里
Stop right there.
什么问题？
And what is that?
菜单上没我的名字
l'm not on the menu.
这还真是大团圆啊
Well, isn't this one big family reunion?
克里斯和克莱儿兄妹
Chris and Claire Redfield.
你们只会妨碍我办事
You've really become quite an inconvenience for me.
我说过我会带朋友同行
l told you l'd be bringing a few friends.
你应该要多带几个
You should have brought more.
克里斯
Claire.
克莱儿
Claire!
Chris!
克莱儿
你
You
想都别想
Don't even think about it.
你是谁？
Who the fuck are you?
想都别想
l don't think so.
不准关门！我可是大制片！
Don't... Don't you shut them. l'm a producer!
快点开门！
Open those doors.
你们等着面对严重的后果吧
You are gonna deal with some serious consequences.
混帐东西！
You motherfuckers.
打开
Open the...
你们会后悔的！你们等着看吧！
You're gonna live to regret this, all of you!
妈呀！
Oh, God.
我只想回家
l just wanna go home.
嘿
Hey...
不会有事的
...it's gonna be okay.
不
No.
克里斯、艾莉丝
Chris! Alice!
快走
Come on!
（净化设施 授权码）
我不希望你错过这个
l didn't want you to miss that.
干的好！
That's right.
明星架势，赞啦！
Star power, bitches.
这是奇迹
lt's a miracle.
我从没想过有这么多人还活着
l never dreamed there would be this many of us left alive.
接下来呢？
So, what's next?
这是亚凯地以紧急频道广播
This is Arcadia, broadcasting on the emergency frequen...
我说
l say...
我们扛下这个使命
...we live up to the promise.
这是亚凯地以紧急频道广播
This is Arcadia, broadcasting on the emergency frequency.
座标西经118点30度 北纬34点05度
Location 118.30 degrees west, 34.05 degrees north.
这里没有感染
There is no infection.
重覆，这里没有感染
Repeat, there is no infection.
我们提供安全、食物和庇护
We offer safety and security, food and shelter.
如果你在外面，我们会帮助你
lf you are out there, we will help you.
一切都还有希望
There is hope.
- 那是什么？ - 麻烦
- What is that? - Trouble.
倒数57秒行动开始
Deployment in T-minus 57 seconds.
降落时注意你们的队形
When you hit the deck, you watch your formation.
不留活口格杀勿论
Take no prisoners and shoot to kill.
敌人数量未知
Total enemy numbers are unknown...
不过其中有雨伞的逃犯和主要目标
...but will include Umbrella fugitives and prime targets.
克莱儿瑞菲尔德、克里斯瑞菲尔德
Claire Redfield, Chris Redfield
还有艾莉丝计划
and Project Alice.
所以各位，不论你们遇见什么
So, people...
只要记得一件事
...whatever's waiting for you out there, just know one thing:
你们是在为自己的生命
You are gonna be in for the fight...
奋战
...of your lives.
嘿！老弟
Hey, boys.
你们男生都这样欺负女生吗？
Is that any way to treat a lady?